The only thing.
Thank
you. Thank you. Thank
you. Rice his
cheeks only came up clowns leave
the stage at White House.
Who is it sirrah. This rice well
be horrified from all of our
nation did I not forbid you to appeal
this mother the one who. Asked
me why I had to call very low. Price
happy who here who indeed donkeys
say Rob I hear high all of
whom. Almost like I'm unhappy
off the stage myself.
Still there. Bombing said first
that his burning five spine if you
do every the one bomb is if
a mole I find your cheeks fall you think
you will protect me or see for the cause
sorry I will not allow you to insult me in
this manner really what matter would you
prefer I have down there will tolerate no
more of this. Go on with the play my free
this is right was that he was the general
retained their seats my sword made by to
their rhythms who is this bright God.
Mike has to see. Whether my fairy
still no exit but he will then I and
we have knife to. All of this fat
stuff to groups.
OK so you don't have
a problem I scavenged Yeah she may put
her tongue out that she was doing.
What. I say Be silent. And I offer one
universal challenge to all but all who
wish to die please raise their hands
approach young heroes I will take your
name to the first man who falls I'll build
a monument who will have
the list you serve. You.
Know anyone. Anyone at all not
one name not one God but
he wrote them grow up.
I tend to me for Moon.
I clap my hands three
times thus. At the. Eclipse You also
write
a while. How dare you. And I insist
I call upon all the noble. This is an outrage
you have an outrage nothing on earth
will move me from this stage three.
Kelley's. The city
where you ask why have you done this to our
month following an admirable act I have
two reasons either what computers. Post
is an abominable act says goes and
says tragic
a second. Robots might see you. But
you you close the play it is not
a very good play. And then the amount of
possible you would like that we turn to
these good people yes yes yes catch.
Myself if I have I organized close up
playing every night instead. Ladies and
gentlemen your money will be returned
highly passed out. The night when I run.
Your house it is an extraordinary
man but oh I agree so how it
philosophy musician I write all
those. And the best sorts me
really know I should
a fuck to become that of telling
me that comic mask that no
Presently he will take it off. No mishear
he keeps. And heaven help the man who
smiles it's. Good.
For Syria. When you leave
Paris. After what you've just
done the most Only if you don't know that
the call to quiche was paid. Was yours.
No no I don't think I
said not to quote acacias
a long long time is long gone by three
feet of steel Yes but I want to scare you
and I go No but you may go. On tell
me why are you staring at my no
no I was not staring does that astonish you
oh no no no I think careful not to love
poem Why not if you please it's disgusting
of them but no I just color appeared to
you on oh so by no means
possible you find it just
a trifle large no small very small tiny
infinitesimal why but you accuse me of
absurdity small my nose why magnificent
my nose to you how do you view but.
Now that I glory in this nose of
mine what a great nose indicates
a great man Gene you courteous
intellectual very courageous
Why was that pace of yours that blanket
glorious cavity which my right hand
finds on top of you is the void
of pride of poetry of soul
a picturesque MOUs of come to
a character of lows in short as that which
at the bottom of that limp spine of
yours my left foot Oh I. Presently
this fellow will grow tired
oh he blows his horn will will no one
put him in his place if you will allow
me observe. This year. You are no use
your nose is
a rather large church. Rather Oh well
is that all full of course you know young
so you're too simple for me you might
have said
a great many things why you waste your
opportunity for example to us aggressive I
sort of that nose were mine I'd have it
amputated on the spot practical How do you
drink with such a move you must have had
a cup made especially descriptive is
a rock a crag a Cape Cape say rather
a Pennines. Inquisitive What is
that receptacles a razor case or
a portfolio kindly do you love the little
bird so much that when they come and sing
to you you give them this to
perch on. Cautious Take care
a weight like that might make you top
heavy eloquent when it blows the typhoon
howls and the clouds doctors
dramatic when it believes. The Red
Sea. The simple when do
they unveil the monument
military they wear
a secret weapon. Enterprising
wonder sighing for some perfume
a. Respectful. I recognize
in you amount of power
a man of you from me that's all literary
or was this the nose that launched
a thousand ships These my dear sir are
things you might have said had you some
tinge of letters out of which to color
your discourse but which are not so you
never had an atom and unless I was you only
but three could write you down. Yes yes
. Yes I'm Dr Duncan.
How do you do and I see how to.
Do their job. Because to come
such and against this cold who
look at you know ribbons no lace
not even gloves true I carry my abdomen
only on my soul that with deeds instead of
ribbons I'm told in my good name and crowned
with the white plume of freedom but
but I have no gloves
a pity too I had one the last one of an
old pair and last that very careless of
some gentleman offered me an
impertinence I left it. In his face
so be. Sure thanks he said to me oh
a poet Maya suppose if you were
so while we fight I'll improvise
a ball out for you and as I am the
refrain. Thrust Oh will you I
will. Think you want to
write like well I want
you all at the fair I'm sure the book
on your between the bear's rock and. A
barbarian What do you mean
by that oh that the typo
I mean my drivers
so there we go. Likely I tossed my how the
way you lined with me or my love for the
cloak that covers my bridle
rein then. I'll solve to work
with. Oh thank you thank you all and.
Thanks five thanks I think thank
you I know why with you thank you.
THANK YOU THANK YOU THANK YOU. Thank you.
Thank you. THANK YOU
THANK YOU THANK YOU Thanks. Thanks
thanks.
Thanks thanks thanks thanks
Michelle I see you in my peacock
THANK YOU THANK YOU THANK YOU THANK
YOU THANK YOU. Thank you better for
your son this brawl of here in the heart
for your living is gay in the belly if you
all so you can show me. Thank.
God From my point floats like this the poem
is ready to drive you back to the wall
then as I did the refrain fast Whoa.
Whoa Farai thank you why did.
You break up you call THANK YOU THANK
YOU THANK YOU Are you allowed to say
something different if I had lost all of
this life for the time being that's where
that's gone so I mean the trying
of my friends who roam free for
a time to the right is recall
that as I am the refrain that.
Great. Friends pray God that
is laudable. And your so.
For your time has come.
Thanks for you want to see
them as I under
a frank THANK YOU THANK
YOU THANK YOU THANK
YOU THANK YOU THANK YOU
THANK YOU THANK YOU.
Thanks thanks. Thanks. Thanks thanks.
THANK YOU THANK YOU THANK YOU
THANK YOU THANK
YOU THANK YOU THANK YOU THANK YOU.
THANK YOU THANK YOU THANK YOU please thank
the performances was the house struck by
the lights when they raised
the money for us tonight. We.
Will go we will watch your pride if you
root you listen to them. Think you mean you
name more for me to be called if you believe
all those markings that don't think he
should probably be the cardinal's nephew
has power there and power here just
for take an example from me twenty years
a captain while others who know only how
to deploy their forces a court not dangle
a marshals back home. Someday I
will avenge you to the impossible
Come on let's go to dinner then I don't
know not why not because I have no money.
But the purse of gold farewell put on open
ocean. And you have until the first of
next month nothing. Yes. But
a moment pardon me here.
I'm not to go hungry.
I have everything here. My dear child I
cannot bend disgust called pride of mind to
accept such
a crime but. Yet for fear that I may
give you pain if I refuse I will
take something. A great.
One of them. And
a glass of water no clear. And. Nothing
more oh yes your hand to kiss.
Thank you.
Idiot. Then I. Think
does
a. More do so I was hungry
abominably. Tell me
anything why do you hate this more for e
a very bad act but come now the real
reason the truth. That fat go to kind of
hold his belly and his still dreams of
being sweetly dangerous some of the women
sighs and languages making sheep's eyes out
of his great frogs face I hate him ever
since one day he did smile upon. Oh
my friend I seem to see over some
flower
a great snail crawling.
Or. Is it possible for
me to love. I love. Me I
know all my love Think about
think of me me whom the
plainest woman would despise me with this
nose of mine that marches on before me by
a quarter of an hour who shall I love by
a process must be the woman in the
world most beautiful looks beautiful
in these eyes of mine
beyond compare. With age
cousin Roxanne this.
Well why not if you love her tell her so
my old friend. Look at me and tell me
how much hope remains for me with this
protuberance and I have no more of you she's
now and then I may grow tender walking
alone in the blue cool of evening to some
god and fresh with flowers after the
benediction of the rain my
poor devil of a nose inhalers
a pretty look and I follow with my
eyes where some boy or girl upon his.
Passes
a patch of silver and I feel somehow. I
wish I had
a woman to walking with me under the
moon and holding my arm and smiling and
then I breathe. And I forget. And
then I see the shadow of my
profile on the wall. My friend.
My friends I have my better days knowing
myself so ugly so alone but you know with
your courage that poor child you just know
if you you didn't if you saw her eyes
did not avoid you. That is
true well then books on her
cell phone watching your jewel pale OK Oh
yes her lips parted her and her breasts
dust I saw each speak speak man.
She might laugh at me. That is the
one thing in this world I feel
down I see it as
a lady outside asking for
you. Who. Do you want to
I have
a message for you from my assistant she
desires to know when and where she may see
you. She has certain things you said
a thing. She wishes to see me we go to
model it dawned him Matheson from the
and October Sky Where
would you suggest. Which.
I am thinking and you think. Will
help with writing Oh yes she said
I reckon I know the pastry could well.
Be Shot All right. But we aren't going
to have an OK until.
I will be there. OK To see
being quite so cruelly
long ago you know that I exist imagine she
is all still seeing the soul now you are
going to be. Like to me a story
a flame I need to fight hold mommy's
all over my head. I have my eyes
I knew the way. Quiet
please she went missing that. Going.
Back. Thank goodness you're still here
what's the matter I'm afraid to go home mom
you know those coming verses I wrote
about the competition sure he's high of
a few only
a hundred of them waiting for me on the way
home they're going to beat me train me
please would you permit me to spend the
night with you the hundred men is that oh
oh. You know if you're going
home tonight. Come from the fly
over I say I'll be that the security or
shut up you I want them to go. To the US I
want. To risk like this pastry cook
first because this pastry cook is
a friend second because
this pastry cook is also
a poet and most important if anything should
happen to this pastry tomorrow morning
at seven his shop will be closed.
I don't read there Aagot.
If you. Think it's.
Live.
Live. Live.
live Live.
Live
.
I don't at the time I'm
not going all right. Brag
a. Little about all those
why. Is it over Oh
really so soon. Or for me I
had my source how many did we
kill oh about eight eight eight zero.
This gentleman begins to annoy me.
This for some meat must write that attention
Marigold in time. Your house of course
needs
a stronger roof learn this proof seven
zero. Zero zero zero zero come eat any of
us well not quite so for now please see
the man without breakfast is like. That
she's changed her mind but would think we
were magnificent last night and it took
us two then as I end the refrain when she
arrives quickly we converse undisturbed
whenever you like my shop is yours the
little dining was making many Rice told God
what
a living thing that's Ike and the
river and she's come I say. Well
.
Above the one we're have you're going to
gesture little one day that you are some.
Oh. Some Jelly Roll. If you
like the order of these in
the sunshine do not retire
until you have finished them.
Lesson about all of this be the hour when
you remember to remember me and came to
tell me what to tell
you. Before I do take.
Are you I wonder still the same big brother
almost that you used to be when we were
children playing by the pond in the old
garden that the Bears run those lovely So
you used to make swords out of the Russian
Uganda lion dolls were golden in those
days I could tell you and you did everything.
For the rocks of the sweet tyrant in
short skirts and long for Cyprus.
To play. Sometimes when you would fall
in or hurt your hand you used to come
running to me and I would be your mother
in say Oh very grown up folks now what
have you been doing to look so let
me say. Oh no wait let me see.
Still at your age now how did you do it
that way with the big boys of the West and
I. Am going to. Wire little mother and
tell me what I washed his blood away how
many you played with know about
a hundred a hundred you are
a mess ten now. Tell me what you
were going to tell me. If you.
I think I do. It seemed so like
those happy days long ago. Yes
how to. Listen. I laughed. There
is someone who does not know.
Someone who loves me but is afraid of me
and keeps away and never says one more.
Good. One hundred. Years he
left me I am sure of it.
And he is still just to win your
own regiment your company S.
. He is noble. Young pray you believe.
You are to me. Nothing. This my family.
I love you so much. And I have never
seen him anywhere except in the.
You have never spoken of. Him
How do you know him well
people talk about what
about you. And I know.
You say it in the god.
His name. And you stand
in. The. He is not in the
god yes since last one.
Is on the lake you come to Paris for
no need. So soon we lose our own.
But who do you have I have
a good lawyer joy in nature and. With my
dear child you will love only words which
were created by for all
you know the man may be
a savage off. With such
as I am ready soon.
Yes well lost souls all written in
all I. CAN DO FOR brought me good
to tell me that I do not care for the stand
but I'm the reason for your confidence
they say that in your company frightened.
You are wrong this column was
a clever with any outsider who in truth and
self is that what you have I am so fake
for not without reason and I thought
you know if you know respect to fear.
You want me to defend your little
down with. Just for me because I have
always been your friend and this is what
you want of me will you be his friend.
And I will be his friend and never love
invited you never promise. I promise
I'll say thank you I knew I
could rely on you. Oh no
I must.
Know you never told me about last
night but you must have been
a hero happy to tell me all the
things and about him so. You know
we are so we know he must
like telling. Us all the
things you should tell me the whole
story so you know we have time.
When my parents.
Let's leave this place for the oil companies
on its way here you know they're on my
heels Naturally I told them all about last
night while you lay off but why did you
stop them.
Dead men in the street scandalous you
know my edict against doing that if you I
expect to have it done Fost for them off
I wish to know who was responsible for
last night's outrage
a plus than if I understand your eminence
that it well and now I have news that
should be more to your liking I
fear in confidence Oh uneasy
armistice with Spain this to my colonel say
your commission has been for Fed Thank
you thank you for one thing was last
night at the theatre the jewel in
rhyme at Guardsman with the nose to bears
an act that impossible is impossible his
treatment of my free vomit over the
arrogance with which he closed the play
credible it would be
a miracle if the bee concert by tomorrow
what would you do with Him Your Eminence
nothing I thought I might leave that to
you to meet kids place him somewhere in
your service with a
comfortable allows He looked
a little threadbare. You but your eminence
you detest doing Also I do why didn't
you prevent it I should much prefer that
Monsieur de Bergerac live by the pen
rather than died by the sword Do
you not agree and flung by all
means arguments by old me. And then.
As I in the room brain. Trust.
Was.
Like. This you better back.
Your excellence. I have
come to express my admiration for both
your exploits last night and day.
Thank you my dear fellow we may have had
differences but I am disposed to forget
that that is very generous of you know
Truly you are seen as a man of many skills
a rare combination soldier and poet
would you care to join my following
most I do not follow. I am told you have
written the play as you know my uncle the
cardinal is also
a dramatist I might help you there zero
zero zero at last you can have performed by
not I could take it to him.
Really cause let me write
a few lines here and there and you'll find
a theater before you read
write my life. Impossible
when he likes a thing he pays well yes
but not so well as when I have made
a line of things and so I pay my so far
hundreds of times you are probably my
friend if you have observed that soon
she would be found in the street almost
stopped in their flight by those fine brutes
to show their tail feathers not up the
man who hired those scoundrels he must be
an angry man today Who was it you know it
was I I hired them to do the sort of
what we do not soil our hands with
punishing and insolent poet they ought
to be mounted before they spoil I know.
So we do not return these
to you all friends.
Have you read Don Quixote I have been found
myself the hero be so good as to read
once more the chapter of the windmill thirty.
Windmills remember if you fight with
them maybe swing round their hill jobs and
cost to down into the mine or up among
the stars came from. Your.
Home you don't know where you made your
fortune I was willing to guess there you go
again grabbing yet this latest pose of
yours ruining every opportunity that comes
your way becomes exaggerated Well then I
exaggerate there are certain things in
this world
a man does well to carry to extreme your
precious independence your white through
night how do you expect to succeed in life
what would you have me do for the people
who just some great man
and like a creeping by on
a tall tree crawl up I cannot
stand alone no thank you be
a buffoon in the vial hope of teasing out
a smile on some cold face no thank you
he took Toad for breakfast every morning
make my knees callous cultivators supple
spine aware of my belly grovelling in the
dust no thank you with my left hand scratch
the back of any swine that groups I'm
going for me by my right to proud to know
his partners business takes in the fee no
thank you shall I use the Fire God gave
me to burn incense all day long no thank
you struggle to insinuate my name into the
columns of those that calculate schema
be afraid of love more
to make a visit than
a poem and seek introductions by Rose in
Bloom says no thank you no no I thank you
and are dear and I thank you. To
see. To laugh to greet me to walk in my
own way free with an eye to see things as
they are a voice that means manhood
to cook my head for I choose at
a word yes and no to fight all
right but to never to make
a line I have not heard in my own heart.
To travel on the road under the sun. Under
the stars nor care to pay more
for to live be on the board.
You know with all modesty to say my
soul be satisfied with flowers we
does with foreign sea from. But got of
I mean the one God and you may call
your own. You know where
I live too proud to be
a part of sight that is my vehicle like
the German grows towering to heaven like
the mountain Pardon me I
stand not high maybe but
a load alone yes but why go about making
enemies watching other people making
friends everywhere as
a dog makes friends I mock the matter
of these canine courtesies I think he
comes Thank Heaven I love it and
he is still this to all the world
and then to me say very softly
that she loves you not.
To be alone for
a moment. So you know light was
your style the fight. Present
play now all this time not all that in
my longest time enough I wanted now.
As an example of
a young tadpole sneaking out the
dollar way you know that. You
addressing me. Yes You lied for the Norman
farmer. You were something of
a lesson machine did whatever your name
I never let you know increase John dead
never let. Nobody lives as you are and
you come here you should know there is
a certain subject or object if you prefer
that is never mentioned among us and that
is look at me. You understand
you mean there's actually never
speak that way. To even breathe it is to
have to do with him he has exterminated
several whose mere tone of voice suggested
you die before your time just mentioned
anything convex or cost imagine this one
word one syllable one gesture namely one's
name and your I could have becomes
you are winding sheets. Captive
So what is the proper thing to do when
you get schools go to books for prove to
them that one may be
a Mormon and still have
courage I thank you. Sir
we all start. Let me say what you were
Jim. I said I will I promise to make those
kind of not knowing whether by the time
you know lives in those narrow back
streets. No more in the sky. Everything
Doc it was so dark more deuce you
could not see beyond your nose.
Who. Is that man.
A new recruit arrived last week.
His name is Cristiano he let.
Me see. Well. As I was
saying. It grew dark.
Because I see your before your eyes. I
started thinking how over the second one
amateur go into road on us whenever
he took on no use for. Ever you took
a notion I've taken I something
to powerful enough to make me go.
Wrong. Let me in my lot of my life now
that I'm here I may as well go through
with gusto your only assault flashed
in the dark I couldn't fail I know.
My late if I knew that I was
robbing knows it. Was my.
Way. You. And I you know
no.
My. Courage that pleases
me why you might know I'm
a brother. Brother.
The distant cousin much the same she has
told you everything she loves me perhaps.
My descent more than I can say on it the
sum of the weeks forgive me if you knew
how much I have had my yes yes yes and all
those mostly my apologies. But sometimes
there's
a letter from me Oh yes why not. For once
I write that ruins everything by because
any schoolboy could write well more
gracefully than I but. You did not attack me
like a. Anyone can pick
a quarrel no I never at
a loss for words among men but with any
woman I was speechless down and one of
those stammering idiots who cannot call
a woman really. As for myself it seems to
me that given the opportunity and if I
put my mind to it. I could do that rather
well or if I had words to say what I have
here were handsome like you together we
could make one mighty hero of romance only
I had your wit.
Borrow it. From me. Would you do
repeat to her the words I gave you day by
day sent to her the letters that I write
now I mean write Central have no disillusionment
come so we will both together for
you Sarah Hoye Jo Why not. Train afraid
that when you have it all alone you will
lose no fear it is yourself she loves
you for yourself put into words
my words upon your lips. Will you. Will
you. Visit me so much to you.
That means a comedy situation for
a poet should we collaborate I would be
your local doctor this year and chanted
sold your ring to charm the Fairy Princess.
Thing because the prize not worth the
danger. My friend.
Like my shall have it all the more plucking
the flowers we've got the plant in the
. Dust Oh I love him I don't.
Know
a dozen ways to read that line. To give
it some meaning any meaning that's why I
love the last two I love the
last why I love me I love the.
Show your smile has known
a perfect thing you are
a white rose where in love lies in ambush
for its natural prey and the garden of my
heart you are the most. The most.
Fragrant blossom. As the
tender SAP thirsts for rain.
As the Eagle seeks this. As the waves
her drums toward the shore my heart
you're singing the. Good you
know you're beginning to have
a feel for. Words I'm sick of those are
your weapons how else do Congo there's one
one when they're fighting in the north
now you know that the regiment could be
called up any day and
I've never even kissed
a person's my boy who has been my she
sees the call the geese as often as she
does me. You suppose she's
playing with me making
a fool of me. Impossible How can
you say how do you know. Sir and.
Ever confidence you could find out.
Nonsense I said. Stop the
tearing but since Cyrano
intelligently discreetly
the with finesse. What do
you think of Cristiano for all these weeks
he's dealing with and I love him good
I do find him intellectual more so than
you Eva Oh I didn't mean oh no no no I am
glad no man ever thinks of those
things that's pretty neat.
Sometimes he falls into
a reverie. Inspiration change. But
then all at once he will say something
absolutely. How like
a man you think because a man
has a handsome face he must be
a fool. This is certainly
a he talks well about. He does
not talk he raps strange.
Only the other night he said to me
extemporaneously my dog will. Take my home I
shall have it all move. Talking the
flowers we will keep the place in blue.
Cross he rides world one day
listen. Knowing you have and still
more heart to do you deny the find heart
room the first is too much hard and too
little just how much heart does he mean
you what. You were jealous Yes poets are
all alike. Would you dare criticize
these laws. Only believe that
unto you my whole heart gives one cry.
And writing tracks down you receive.
Sending your kisses through my
fingers. Leaving only read my letter
with you. Yes those lost lives
of the but he overwrites
Listen to this you know them all by
heart everything from I may call that
flattering is
a mast oh oh oh yes I must
must. If you will. When
there was
a lot of reading how many problems use of
poetry must this new book you only use
before I do not know. My friend you
men own the world and all that in.
Woman Is it best to prize a property
valued much the same as a horse or
a dog one like the pear and sheen of skin
and soundness of teeth and limb Well if
I must be chattel then the term should be
mine and the price according to my own
values the.
Christiane tells me the Jew
me tonight. You have to
speak about. One thing. And
everything I should say
Speak to me of love in your own
way. Impreza says I. Am like.
But you will not attend. The
book and I damn well know.
That. This year.
With. Me.
Hold still time to let your life know that
some brilliant phrases sent no. I have
no more of my words my sentences
all from you making our love
a little comedy don't you Rick it was
a game at first but now she care. Thanks
to you I'm not afraid any longer Ah speak
for myself oh and i will you shall
see they sides I know one of the day
a woman in my arms and tonight I will.
Thank you my friends and good box job
I beg you to leave may be your making
a grave. So be it.
Christine Roxanne. I
am so glad you. Missed
a house here in the morning.
The South has. To do.
Now. Speak to me. I love you. Yes to me.
I. Love you now be eloquent
be brilliant for me tonight.
I love you. So. You have used
the improvisers friends
I love you. Very much.
And I ask for cream and you give
me milk. Tell me first. How.
Very much. Is that all you
vote for only I might
Christiane but Roxanne I love you
again no not again I do not love you.
That respect. I. I adore you.
I know I go and search and that distresses
me as much as if you had grown and.
Please gather your dreams
together into words. I
I know you love me good night the request
when I was going to say that you would do
on me yes I know that
don't know I go away.
A great success. Hopefully speak
for yourself my friend why I can't
well at least you know not to take
a woman in your office or home
please let them make your love
a little comedy post your own I cannot
live unless I win her back now this mobile
home of the devil and I can teach you
about all this money. And wind. Up
a certain old house. Dusty very dark well.
There's more than you deserve. For this
crime can be done stand over there.
If you hear before about me I whisper
you want to say here's. Roxanne.
Roxanne I. Was called.
Christian you were good I had to tell you
you know the way you tell me you know.
You do love me anymore. No not
anymore I LOVE YOU ever more.
And ever more and more. Bullets that.
Love grows and struggles like an
angry child. Breaking my heart. His
cradle this is still here. But such
a thing is dangerous why not
have smothered you. And so I do
and yet he lives. I found as you
shall you shall find. This new
born babe and in front.
Good strong enough.
To strangle those two serpents
down there and I. I am very.
Only tell me why you speak so haltingly
as your imagination go play.
Do. You want to know it has
a. War with some of whom
they grow in darkness or the
light of you. My words are heavy
with heavy like returning the. Yet
they must fly so high come nearer them
standing on the bank snow then I'll come
down. Why so great and. Let me
enjoy the one moment I ever.
My one chance to speak to you
and see. And see this yes night
making all things dimly beautiful one veil
over us both you need no eyes to hear my
heart oh To night I did seem as if I speak
for the first time. For the first time
yes. Your voice it is not the same shouldn't
I have another voice tonight my own
myself very. Close by my heart
is anyone that you dare ask for
you therefore my heart has given me time
for you word sentence and phrases. Nothing
not sweet spot you brings nothing of sweet
for you and me tonight. Can never spoke
to me See I tell you there comes one moment
one cent Heaven help those who passed
the moment by when beauty
stands looking into the SO with
a great reader. That
sicken and pretty well.
That is. Going to be on the breast beyond
reason beyond love's own power of loving
your name is like
a golden bear will come in my heart and
when I think of you I tremble and the bells
swaying from the ring. On my
very. Next.
Is. That his love of wind of
terrible and generous beauty.
Storing blinding music. You may take my
happiness to make you happier even though
you never know I do but you only let me
hear sometimes it's all over the distance
of your joy. Do you begin to understand
a little and you feel my soul there in
the darkness bring the new. Holy tonight
now I dare say these things I tell you and
you hear them. It is my voice Martin my
own but my son there in the green
room above me for you to tremble as
a blossom along the way to tremble and I
can feel all the way down along this just
me but I was with you when all
over the passion of you. Said to.
A week when I love you and I
am yours and you have made me.
Just.
Only let me ask one thing
more. If. You ask me
yes this is
a. I mean. Come. On I mean. I I
ask. I know I ask too much.
This is. All. A much more than
all I know I stop you I ask
I ask
a very few. I am angry with myself
because I know I go too far and
so I say to myself.
Say I am looking for the house of Madame
Rock Central that this is not the house
that way to the right to the right thank
you sir I shot straight might be true you
do the dirty lies. With the second. Sooner
or later. The.
Smaller it must be so. Young.
Must be. Able to be
myself the cause of the.
Few still there yes. We were speaking of.
This. And obviously just when all is done.
About taken before the shrine of memory
a rosy not over a secret
whispered to a smooth as a shoe
a moment later more over
the Russia with some seed
a sacrament of blossoms the new songs sung
by two hearts to an old Super Bowl to
you. By one chase. No.
No shame then you can.
Gather your sacred bus.
Your moment maybe more.
Books.
But before.
That I have something here that is
my mouth. Was not mine. I spoke
to the one. She kisses. My work.
Six.
But on the last Joe way to where she lives
here Madame robot that's what you said
the last go on will be our young girl but
overall but I'm too old to change while
my big brother say. Oh but I'm
sure there's somebody. When
it is eleven by the young lady how
much the room that grow like. The old.
Mother I love you yes
yes. Puffing by cousin
I saw this like. That but profitable to
the shone of the you don't belong to
a big reason.
Father this letter concerns you. Not
on the cardinal will have his way
although against your will that is
why I am sending this to you by
a most. Intelligent discreet
you will communicate to him
Our order to perform here and at
once the right call. Holy match.
You and Christiane will be married privately
in your house. He resigned to the
Congress can and who sends here with his
blessings you are very humble in the
statute. Oh this is terrible.
For your to be the I
am to be the bride. Or
look here house can.
Give to the monastery in My Name one hundred
and twenty pieces of CO four hundred
and twenty
a whole lot of every
word. Resign your show
I am Lisa.
Is coming to him and about
him and do we need clean.
Water today me why where did you come from.
From the man I have just returned from
a man who was mad like
a bomb I tell you my friend from the now
see how I say the mold very well say soul
bang raising man to. A
rabbi My guess what we see
a complete let me pass his face
would have a smile. My heart
a lady is waiting for me this is
very. Near Oh there is no excuse
my appearance I have arrived
by the last from the boat
a trifle singed as I passed through the.
Mist sure enough will be now I will show
you which looks my only flexible and have
the culture of its surface if I desire no
such thing I go slow. So you need to
know by what mysterious means I reach
people who they secret a fear of
state above to confidentially
a new invention of my own drunk true as
well as I know knowing through I had my
choice of several inventions Yes several
ways to violate the Virgin skies
several save it. As for
instance smoke having
a natural tendency to rise blowing the
globe enough to raise me. Here step makes
one again on my computer Paroxetine the
shape of my huge no cost driven by impulses
I put in
a small piece from the rear and thus speed
up plugs I think about yes I know that I
finally seated on an iron plate very long
legged into the ear of the eye and. I
catch the magnet throw it again and so
proceed indefinitely excellent and which to
do with. Why none of them yet another
which was.
Guess. I can't. Try. And
interesting it is this.
And you guessed it yet I know is it.
Last you will never know but no matter how
you are free on the way out oh man when
I drunk that horse I know Cyrano this
very moment they have exchanged.
My C.O. Come loose. You all so I have
a lot in space my lot the handsome couple
you want got talking together quite so.
That kindly beat jaws husband fair will
your regiment leave tonight some report
that bunch. Of the cadets in the cause
they ought to be and under my command. Out
there we may have an account to you somehow
that news fails to disquiet. Here in
the office about all
deliver this. Christian.
The bridal night is not so nice. Somehow
that it was fails to disquiet me.
Oh you have your letters.
Or some. Take everything for me promise
me never to let him do anything dangerous
I'll do my best economic problems but just
very boldly making the camp Yes yes I'll
try basic cable Yes if possible.
To me every single day that
I promise you.
The situation is simple gentleman we have
beseeched address the prince of Spain has
besieged us Consequently we all sit around
on war for the procedures of see them
starve to death yes but
the marshal has devised
a brilliant plan for bringing in food
this very night now see here spare is the
details could really unfold us with the
food truth we are hungry for five like me I
am only your cook. Oh yes
I know you to call me
a politician. I can afford
a job takes my conduct under fire as well
know it was only yesterday I would tell
the Spanish attack pouring my men down
like an avalanche I myself lead the charge
and your white star of.
The road. Where she goes.
And go Hi Scott. I don't ever so yes I
was so far in advance I was in danger of
being captured but I thought quickly took
off and flung away the stuff that marked
my military rank and so being in conspicuous
escaped among my own force relative
return and when the day when your state or
better still an officer does not like to
resign the privilege of being
a target how pleasant for you that you are
denied that privilege pleasant let me
ask God with your permission I would leave
the first charge tonight wearing it over
my shoulder what bluster your safe making
that offer and you know it my scarf lies
on the river bank between the lines
a spot swept by artillery
impossible to reach alive yes.
Here are. The thank you. This
bit of white is what I need to make
a sick. I was hesitating.
You have decided me. Stand
up are going to fire a man down there
running away yes a Spaniard. Very useful as
a spy both sides. As I was about to tell
you possible is withdrawn more than pop up
for you Fortunately the sun you do not
know that if they do not and they will
attack to night at this point. The
river I make no break pretense in
loving you but since you gentlemen esteem
yourselves invincible the bravest of the
brave and all that bind it with the person
on the marshal need to the bush and I
serve him in choosing as I choose
measurements he kept in the great thing is to
gain time to hold until the marshal returns
and to gain time. You will all be so
kind as to lay down your lives.
It. Works on.
Electricity there well that might. Have
taken the liberty of.
Quite. This little spot spot yes but here.
Is nothing the poet what he writes is like
a lover in his lady's office believe in
his imagination everything seems real
There's half
a charm of writing. I made this letter
so pathetic that I was writing it.
For years because it is
a little thing to die.
Not to see. Terrible.
I shall never. Remember. Didn't either.
Good evening of the
King's service you will.
Tell us. Why you know you are we are going
to and why I'm right so I came up here
the Spaniards I thought the
fair but they were mystified.
Why did you come here and do this this thing
they said in Paris that was going back
to. The South. It was Europe.
Think
a little bit as you were pretty. How
many times every day every day. And
each one on. All this for
a few absurd love letters ash
absurd your letters now never.
Everyone was like hearing your voice that
night in the dark remember like your arms
around me. I write them over
and over every page was like
a petal fallen from your soul
like the light from the fire of
a great love sweet and strong
and true sweet stroll true.
I came here to ask you this. It is
time to be forgiven now when we may
die so soon. Forgive me for being light
and they may not be new Only because you
have some for now oh. I love you
for yourself. What you are.
How you must have suffered for you saw how
frivolous I was and to be loved for them
. Costume for the poor casual body went
about two or so like you that must've been
taught to know. Still. You
can
a perfectly believe in me or I love my best
I want no love like this I want love only
only for what every woman sees in you I
can do better know if it was best before.
You to have to get the
know. I was a child I'm
a woman. If you were less hands lol
unattractive ugly even I should get use
to. You mean that I do. Ugly even.
Think only Cyrano. Serena.
He has something to
tell you. Where you go
I will return in my.
Search. Your wife so she goes with me also
she remains there is still time for her
to escape she stays but it will give me
a bus can I stay here also so you should
go to watch Ally run away and leave
a woman. Like come and such. Like.
Listen to her. She does not love
me. Think about she loves you
enough she loves only my soul know yes
that means you and your love. I see
when you. Go every day every day.
Simple simple for. Month even blockaded
How did you send all those letters are they
like I managed to say that everything.
Love. This.
Cover so no point to buy. Would love me
if I were ugly she said that yes
i'll. Not still not believe in
such madness go back to you never will be
I may know it is you she loves that is
what we shall see no better choose between
a stop everything when you touch I ruin
your happiness because I was born with
a pretty face and I to ruin yours because
I happen to have power to save what you
perhaps be open. To me to find I'm tired
of being my own Bible I secretary take and
be I'm not actually I want for love for the
poor fool that I. Am going through with
this I'll know one way or the
other. Go tell it or choose what.
Will be. My hopes will.
Happen. Bank fires are going out.
Again in
a disco where Sara kept. Let me go now my
voice around the knows the terrain you
know the line oh do I please
allow me. Very well know
from which direction the advance
comes their way to numbers.
So there's just things. Chris just
things you ought to know that when I do.
He still doubts what I told
him just now I saw there. Was
a crew which I don't just know it was true.
I said that I should love him even if
he was. The word comes
hard before me. Saying I
shall be heard again even
they should. Be good for
to speak. Even. Ask. How
could he ever be courteous
ever to me but you could love him
so as much as yes and move. On.
What is it. How they can
think. What is happening
especially as
a bad ass. There is time which is
Christian of the better that. Covers.
What is it that you wish to. Believe me
this is difficult for one side like words.
John asked me to he told me.
Your place is just. No dying we live.
There and know. To you yes
what I've told. You about you.
It's my duty. I stand. Here's the test.
Yes.
From you must go now. To no
one else knew we. Was you
know to hear your source of. Power
deeper than we knew. Some of.
The so magnificently tell. Us some.
Cookies to. School tomorrow.
Or I am dead and my love poems for
me does not know. You never know.
A place. Going. Down or is high.
To death to avenge no. Peace jobs.
Thank you
thank you.
Thank you.
Lynn.
We know I'm being loving and he obviously
was so common that one spotted by
a man like
a then when all seemed lost we heard the
comforts of our returning to the Back home
of our. Own you have been fortunate to
see adventure ecu have lived by we we
waste our youth there is no wara no hope
for it. Oh for any my son I have just
realized that we are both photos but mine
is the greater folly for I am an overflow
what is more. Everything I told you was
a lie. Mother
satire for the Gazette this for nothing
to love flung in the face of power why do
you do it to know why do you attack stupidity
seek to corruption. I'm too old to
change I'm an old dog with nothing left but
used to have the teeth can be pulled I
can be painful. That him someone rich that
scoundrel sure. This time has gone
too far I swear the scientists are.
And over the deliberate just so on the still
very powerful My friend there are many
ways
a man can die who knows. Maybe
it was an accident. So.
To kill that death how long will you
continue to remain here for every morning.
For it. Was Christian all that. He
knew and you would not ask his last
letters to my home. And see it on
no do you see him often every week
my old friend takes the place of my
kids then brings me all the news. Every
Saturday under that tree. I wait for him
and broke. The hour strikes I need not
tend to look at the last stroke I erase
came back the more he said tires have made
him many enemies but they still fear
that sort of has. No one day touch him
that may be so. It is not violence
I feel for him but solitary
poverty old gray December stealing
one will speak into his dark and. It
seems to me is one the same old coat for
many months yet it's nothing strange in
this world you need not pity Obama he lives
his life his own life his own way the
word and deed free my Lord
Oh yes I know I have old
family member the next. Day I
should be proud to shake his hand.
And you will live to see you again come
whenever you like then you have forgiven me
. I mean. You know when
a man wins everything in this world when
he succeeds too much he feels somehow
thousand small own displeasures with
himself whose home son is not quite remote
but rather a sort of.
Discussed draw you do painter
a great case now and then I envy
goes. The sentiment as your wife.
But I think I must tell you that it is
true that no one has yet dared to attack
your friend Cyrano Nevertheless at the
theatre last night I heard some things.
Keep him at Hobart OK tomorrow when you see
him tell him to be careful I thank you
.
Very much. Sir no you're not really. Do
not do me here with me my regrets I have
a blanket was the grocery Bob was
a gift from my brothers to be
sure. Tempers and playing no.
I was only. A stall a C.
Word for you know what the devil was he
doing there that one he stole it up. The
taste and played well beautifully
and laughed and laughed off it.
As genius Christiane looks.
To me it was always this.
For my friend.
That you. Are you were missing me yes
you'll miss your don't know and some
oh my scribble by.
Wife. It is very. Good to be
quiet all those. Temps to
rise it will die.
Mr system.
What is the matter with you. Should I tell
you something just. Yesterday Friday if
. I ate meat again. Yes I know
that is why you are so pale
please come to me to the effect before you
go and make your great pool of hot soup
not because the costs are quite reasonable
today perhaps you will convert me to no
other world. And I think of it that is so
you bursting with holiness and yet you
never pretty much astonished and now
I shall astonish you. I'm going to
lead to pray for me to night
at best pose. Absolutely
trucks. I did not wait for you to
say.
How may the devil of Miami if I could ever
hope to see the end of that embroidery
after fourteen years late for
the face to face yes madam.
I was detained by
a visitor most unexpected. An
old friend of mine. At least
a very old acquaintance did you tell him
to go away for the time being yes. I said
excuse me. This is Saturday I have
a previous engagement one I
cannot miss. Even for you.
Come back an hour off from your friend
will have to wait I shall not let you go
till dark. Helps
a little before. I must go.
Then tell me now the Course you
Mike is that. For. Me see.
Saturday the nineteenth. The King family
allow for eight helpings of great mama
laid. Very mama laid will
no longer be so cold. Some
day. A royal posts is now normal. One day
everyone was talking about the success of
more years new play. To the day. The King
family left us six
helpings of model address
a. Room plus they were no
longer be so. Wouldn't stay
the course to Fiesta spoke to
Mme de more. She said. No.
Those day. Friday madam
don't said yes. Saturday.
Twenty. Cyrano you what is
it you Cyril now.
Has no money no room to go sometimes
my pondering over there's no.
Use to go. To school.
We all have our own. I have mine.
And he's changed it's quite
right. Talk to me. Not
to. Let her. Do not promise me that
some day he would let me. Read it.
Let us try Jewish it.
OK To me.
Because today. I know that it
will be today in my own dearly
beloved. My hearts to be with
the love I have not told.
Myself by. Coming. No more shall my eyes
drink the sight of you Mike was.
Never a mole with a love that is
a kiss. All over the sweet drinks
of how you read his letter I
remember now the way you are pushing back
a locker with one hand from your heart and
my heart cries out easily rise out and
she was crying when you read
it so well my dear my D.M.S.
I own hearts own my own in
such high. School I remember
hearing on. I am never away.
Even now I shall not leave you.
In another world I shall still be the one
who loves you love zeal beyond measure
beyond.
That how can you read.
And all those fourteen
years excuse me old friend came to
me to get new. Books. It was he.
Moves and I might have known it every time
I heard you speak it was not it was you
I swear. Let it stand it was
you. And the dear Polish woman
that was here. And then Maurice in
the dark that Orsi my life and the
SO. That was. I never. Yes your love to
me even now you. Twice are right
over by own their love I
love you. I hear Silent
so many you see only one. Every night
every day you could mean nothing.
If you knew. You knew when they
looked like on my face. Your teeth.
You knew they were your teeth. Was.
Here is here. What recklessness Oh I
knew it was cured himself I will hear.
That Thank you for what you said. I did not
finish my guess at. Saturday the twenty
six an hour or so before dinner. Died.
Cyrano want to feed them to her fate love
the just hold me ambushed taken away
my noble fellow Alack
a battlefield I guess.
Seems too logical to have
missed everything even my.
Fifty six day do not go
away I may not be here when
you return. Then I love you.
But in the story. When beauty said I
love you to the beast all his ugly Mish
changed and dissolved like magic.
You see. I am still the same
and I have to stop you. Oh my
fault my coming. I have never
known womanhood and its weakness but for
you. My mother did not like you look at me
. I never had
a sister. Sweet. Mockery but
I aspire. But because of you.
I have had across my life.
One whispering silk or. Even
one. I have lost touch.
But. I would not have you mourning
you the lists could Cristiano.
But perhaps. I ask only this. In
the great cold gathers around my
bones. To make you. Meaning
to go with those leaves.
But for you. I for two of. My. Own.
Blind but no one has any.
Already. Shot with modern. Gloves
with lead. Anywhere let the
old fellow come now shows
I'm free on my feet. When.
He's just. Seen now he grins
looking at my nose that Scott.
Was. Hundred against one
a you know that my patient
enemy is. Compromise
cowardice that surrender no never never.
I knew you would overthrow me
and you know I thank my life I.
Own my love those who serve
in the way. My roses.
In spite of you that is one crown away
with me. Tonight when I enter before God.
For you. Sweep away the star of the
blue threshold. One thing without
staying. I'm spotted from
the world. In spite of doom
My know. About.
Why. You.
Are.